<?xml version="1.0" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="106" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/NMC-TBone/xml-schema/main/modDesc.xsd">
    <author>w33zl</author>
    <version>1.1.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Seasonal Prices</en>
        <de>Saisonale Preise</de>
        <fr>Prix Saisonniers</fr></title>
    <description>
<en><![CDATA[
Just as the weather changes with the seasons, so does the supply and demand of various products. Keep an eye on the market to catch the best prices during the year. It might be worth the time and money to invest in seeds or lime well in advance before the planting season starts.

FEATURES:
- More realistic pricing over the year with seasonal variation added for additional filltypes.
- The variation of prices makes each year slightly different and the game will feel less static.
- Products like TMR, fuel and herbicide that normally have fixed prices will now get support for seasonal variation (due to console limitations this only affects sell price).
- Base prices are not changed, whatever base price is set by the map and other mods is maintained.

SUPPORTED FILLTYPES:
- FORAGE, PIGFOOD, DIESEL, ELECTRICCHARGE, METHANE, LIME, FERTILIZER, LIQUIDFERTILIZER, HERBICIDE, SILAGE_ADDITIVE, MINERAL_FEED

_______________________________________________________________________________

COMPATABILITY NOTE:
Due to the hotfix needed because of the base game bug causing some mods that change the same filltype to cause errors (e.g. this together with "BigBags Everywhere" mod), this mod now -unfortunately- overrides the behavior of BigBags Everywhere, resulting in pig food being spawned as pallets being instead of big bags. 

If you still want to have pig food spawning as big bags you need the optional "Seasonal Prices (BigBag Patch)" mod, this will restore the behavior of BigBags Everywhere mod.

_______________________________________________________________________________

CHANGELOG:

v1.1:
- HOTFIX: Compatabillity patch with other mods changing e.g. PIGFOOD (see notes above) [#11]
- NEW: It is now possible to spawn pigfood as pallets
]]></en>

<de><![CDATA[
So wie das Wetter sich mit den Jahreszeiten ändert, so ändert sich auch das Angebot und die Nachfrage nach verschiedenen Produkten. Behalten Sie den Markt im Auge, um die besten Preise im Laufe des Jahres zu erzielen. Es kann sich lohnen, rechtzeitig vor Beginn der Pflanzsaison in Saatgut oder Kalk zu investieren.

FEATURES:
- Realistischere Preisgestaltung über das Jahr hinweg mit zusätzlichen saisonalen Schwankungen für zusätzliche Fülltypen.
- Die Variation der Preise macht jedes Jahr ein wenig anders und das Spiel wird sich weniger statisch anfühlen.
- Produkte wie TMR, Treibstoff und Herbizide, die normalerweise feste Preise haben, erhalten nun Unterstützung für saisonale Variationen (aufgrund von Konsolenbeschränkungen betrifft dies nur den Verkaufspreis).
- Die Basispreise werden nicht verändert, der durch die Karte und andere Mods festgelegte Basispreis wird beibehalten.

UNTERSTÜTZTE FÜLLTYPEN:
- FUTTERMITTEL, SCHWEINEFUTTER, DIESEL, ELEKTROLADUNG, METHAN, KALK, DÜNGER, FLÜSSIGDÜNGER, HERBIZID, SILAGE_ZUSATZ, MINERALFUTTER

_______________________________________________________________________________

HINWEIS ZUR KOMPATIBILITÄT:
Aufgrund des Hotfixes, der aufgrund des Fehlers im Basisspiel notwendig wurde, der bei einigen Mods, die den gleichen Fülltyp ändern, zu Fehlern führt (z.B. dieser Mod zusammen mit dem "BigBags Everywhere"-Mod), überschreibt dieser Mod nun -unglücklicherweise- das Verhalten von BigBags Everywhere, was dazu führt, dass Schweinefutter als Paletten statt als Big Bags gespawnt wird.

Wenn Sie immer noch Schweinefutter als Big Bags spawnen wollen, benötigen Sie die optionale "Seasonal Prices (BigBag Patch)" Mod, diese wird das Verhalten von BigBags Everywhere Mod wiederherstellen.

_______________________________________________________________________________

CHANGELOG:

v1.1:
- HOTFIX: Kompatibilitätspatch mit anderen Mods, die z.B. PIGFOOD ändern (siehe Anmerkungen oben) [#11]
- NEW: Es ist jetzt möglich, Schweinefutter als Paletten zu spawnen
]]></de>
<fr><![CDATA[
Tout comme le temps change avec les saisons, l'offre et la demande de divers produits évoluent également. Gardez un œil sur le marché pour bénéficier des meilleurs prix au cours de l'année. Il peut être intéressant d'investir du temps et de l'argent dans des semences ou de la chaux bien avant le début de la saison de plantation.

CARACTÉRISTIQUES :
- Des prix plus réalistes tout au long de l'année avec des variations saisonnières ajoutées pour des types de remplissage supplémentaires.
- La variation des prix rend chaque année légèrement différente et le jeu sera moins statique.
- Les produits comme le TMR, le carburant et l'herbicide, qui ont normalement des prix fixes, seront désormais pris en charge pour les variations saisonnières (en raison des limitations de la console, cela n'affecte que le prix de vente).
- Les prix de base ne sont pas modifiés, les prix de base fixés par la carte et d'autres mods sont maintenus.

TYPES DE REMPLISSAGE SUPPORTÉS :
- FOURRAGE, ALIMENTS POUR PORCS, DIESEL, CHARGE ÉLECTRIQUE, MÉTHANE, CHAUX, ENGRAIS, ENGRAIS LIQUIDE, HERBICIDE, ADDITIF D'ENSILAGE, ALIMENTATION MINÉRALE.

_______________________________________________________________________________

NOTE DE COMPATIBILITÉ :
En raison du correctif nécessaire à cause du bug du jeu de base causant des erreurs à certains mods qui modifient le même type de remplissage (par exemple, ce mod avec le mod "BigBags Everywhere"), ce mod remplace maintenant -malheureusement- le comportement de BigBags Everywhere, ce qui fait que la nourriture pour cochons est produite sous forme de palettes au lieu de big bags.

Si vous souhaitez toujours que la nourriture pour cochons soit produite sous forme de big bags, vous devez utiliser le mod optionnel "Seasonal Prices (BigBag Patch)", qui rétablira le comportement du mod BigBags Everywhere.

_______________________________________________________________________________

CHANGELOG :

v1.1 :
- HOTFIX : patch de compatibilité avec d'autres mods modifiant par exemple PIGFOOD (voir notes ci-dessus) [#11].
- NOUVEAU : Il est maintenant possible de produire des pigfoods sous forme de palettes.
]]></fr>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_ZYX_SeasonalPricesXP.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <fillTypes filename="xml/maps_fillTypes.xml"/>
</modDesc>